Marist Student Government Association Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 26. 2010
  - Subseries 26.4: Allocations
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - SGA Allocations (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - SHRM Allocations (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - SIFE Allocations (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Sigma Tau Delta Allocations (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Singers Allocations (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Marist College Sirens Allocations (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Social Work Association Allocations (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - SPC Allocations (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - St. Jude Committee Allocations, November 3, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Student Life Council Allocations (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Theta Delta Chi Allocations (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Ultimate Frisbee Club Allocations (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Unknown Allocations (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 26.5: Reports
    - Top 10 Issues for Division 1 Institutes, July 23, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - NCAA Self-Study Guidelines, August 18, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - NCAA Tentative Written Plan (2), August 24, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Steering Committee NCAA, August 1, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - SGA Suggestions, September 28, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Athletics Certification Process (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - NCAA Glossary of Terms (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - NCAA Plan Outline (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - NCAA Self-Study Handbook (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - NCAA Self-Study Instrument (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - NCAA Self-Study Report Instrument (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Campaigning Guidelines 2010, February 1, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Marist Haiti Relief Fund, March 16, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Transition Update (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Subseries 26.6: Misc.
    - Unity Messaging (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Omni Update Instructions (Box 23, Folder 39)
- 27. 2011
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, events, allocations, reports, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 27.1: Meetings
    - Board of Trustees Meetings (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Summer Session (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Subseries 27.2: Legislation
    - Legislation, April 13, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Transportation Committee, April 27, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, May 4, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 27.3: Events
    - Orientation Schedule (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - SGA Transition Banquet, April 1, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 27.4: Allocations
    Extent: 44 folders
    - Advertising Club Allocations (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Alpha Kappa Psi Allocations (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau Allocations (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - American Chemical Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Anime Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Asian Alliance Allocations (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Business Club Allocations (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Chess Club Allocations (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - The Circle Allocations (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Circle K Allocations (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Class of 2012 Allocations (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Class of 2013 Allocations (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Class of 2014 Allocations (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Communication Arts Club Allocations (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Commuter Student Council Allocations (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Computer Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Dance Ensemble Allocations (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Fashion Inc. Allocations (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Game Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Generator Magazine Allocations (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Greek Advisory Council Allocations (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Greek Music Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Habitat for Humanity Allocations, Fall 2011 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Italian American Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Kappa Lambda Psi Allocations (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - LGSA Allocations (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - MCCTA Allocations (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - MCTV Allocations (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - PRSSA Allocations (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Red Ink Allocations (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - SGA Allocations (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Singers Allocations (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Student Life Association Allocations (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Social Work Association Allocations (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Tau Beta Sigma Allocations (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Unknown Allocations (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Subseries 27.5: Reports
    - Board Reports, April 17-18, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Board Reports, May 1, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - NCAA Academic Progress Rate 2010-2011, December 1, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Subseries 27.6: Correspondence
    - President Andrew Paulsen Letter, Summer 2011 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Subseries 27.7: Misc.
    - 2011 Activities Calendar (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Making the Connection - SGA (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Matthew Lubrano Speeches (Box 24, Folder 56)
- 28. 2012
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, allocations, reports, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 28.1: Meetings
    - Full Board Meeting, Spring 2012 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - SGA Joint Meetings (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Subseries 28.2: Allocations
    Extent: 54 folders
    - Advertising Club Allocations (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau Allocations (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - American Chemical Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Anime Society Allocations (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - ARCO Allocations (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Asian Alliance Allocations (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Athletic Training Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Allocations (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Black Student Union Allocations (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Business Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Chess Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The Circle Allocations (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Class of 2012 Allocations (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Class of 2013 Allocations (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Class of 2014 Allocations (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Class of 2015 Allocations (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Class of 2016 Allocations (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Communication Arts Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Commuter Student Council Allocations (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Computer Society Allocations (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Criminal Justice Society Allocations (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Dance Ensemble Allocations (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Fashion Inc. Allocations (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Financial Board '12 Reallocation Report, Fall 2012 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Fox P.A.W. Allocations (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Game Society Allocations (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - The Generator Allocations (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Greek Music Society Allocations (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Habitat for Humanity Allocations (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Italian American Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - International Students Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Kappa Lambda Psi Allocations (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - LGSA Allocations (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Literary Arts Society Allocations (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - MCCTA Allocations (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - MCTV Allocations (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - PRSSA Allocations (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Psychology Club Allocations (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Red Ink Allocations (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Marist College Republicans Allocations (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - SHRM Allocations (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - SIFE Allocations (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Sigma Tau Delta Allocations (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Marist Singers Allocations (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Social Work Association Allocations (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Theta Delta Chi Allocations (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Zeta Psi Allocations (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Subseries 28.3: Reports
    - Dennis Murray: Spring Update on College Activities, January 21, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Improvement Plan (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Subseries 28.4 Correspondence
    - Andrew Paulson Letter of Recommendation, January 12, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Subseries 28.5: Misc.
    - SLA '12-'13 Calendar (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Student Life Association E-board (Box 25, Folder 54)
- 29. 2013
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, allocations, reports, and misc.
  - Subseries 29.1: Meetings
    - Joint Meetings (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - President's Cabinet Meetings (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 29.2: Legislation
    - Student Sustainability Committee, September 11, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Legislation, October 23, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Multi-Cultural Relations Committee, November 6 and 20, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, December 4, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Andrew Basset as Resident Justice (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 29.3: Allocations
    Extent: 73 folders
    - Advertising Club Allocations (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau Allocations (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - American Chemical Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Anime Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - ARCO Allocations (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Asian Alliance Allocations (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Athletic Training Club Allocations (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Allocations (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - BSU Allocations (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Business Club Allocations, November 19, 2019 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Chess Club Allocations (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - The Circle Allocations (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Circle K Allocations (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Class of 2014 Allocations (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Class of 2015 Allocations (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Class of 2016 Allocations (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Class of 2017 Allocations (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Communication Arts Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Commuter Student Council Allocations (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Computer Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Criminal Justice Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Dance Ensemble Allocations (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Marist Democrats Allocations (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Enactus Allocations (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Fashion Inc. Allocations (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Fencing Club Allocations (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Fox P.A.W. Allocations (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Fox Photography Allocations (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Game Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Generator Magazine Allocations (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Greek Council Allocations (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Habitat for Humanity Allocations (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Heart 1 Allocations (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Italian American Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - International Students Club Allocations (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Kappa Kappa Psi Allocations (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Kappa Lambda Psi Allocations (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - LGSA Allocations (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Literary Arts Society Allocations (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - MCCTA Allocations (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - MCTV Allocations (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Phi Alpha Theta Allocations (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Political Science Club (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Pre-Vet Club Allocations (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - PRSSA Allocations (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Psychology Club Allocations (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Marist Republicans Allocations (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Red Ink Allocations (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Sigma Tau Delta Allocations (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Social Work Association Allocations (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Student Life Association Allocations (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Tau Beta Sigma Allocations (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Theta Delta Chi Allocations (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Zeta Psi Allocations (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 29.4: Reports
    - Student Body President's Report, April 16, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 29.5: Misc.
    - Steve Townsend Move-In Day Speech (Box 27, Folder 15)
- 30. 2014
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, events, and allocations
  - Subseries 30.1: Meetings
    - Winter Session Meetings Summaries, January 19, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 30.2: Events
    - 2014 Elections, Fall 2014 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Club Awards, April 16, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 30.3: Allocations
    Extent: 16 folders
    - Anime Society Allocations (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Asian Alliance Allocations (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Allocations (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Class of 2014 Allocations (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Class of 2016 Allocations (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Fox P.A.W. Allocations (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Fox Photography Allocations (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Game Society Allocations (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - PRSSA Allocations (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Red Ink Allocations (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Sigma Tau Delta Allocations (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Society for Human Resource Management Allocations (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Zeta Psi Allocations (Box 27, Folder 35)
- 31. 2016
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to clubs
  - Subseries 31.1: Clubs
    - Kappa Kappa Psi By-laws, Fall 2016 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- 32. Undated
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to legislation, clubs, events, reports, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 32.1: Legislation
    - Amendments to Article II of the SGA Constitution (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Bill for the Class Officers Appointment Process (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - By-laws Amendments (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Campus Ministry Proposal (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Committee Club Capping (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Constitution Committee's Proposed Amendments (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Executive order #02 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Proposed Guidelines for SGA Historian (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Proposed Change in Dean's List Standard (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 32.2: Clubs
    - Circle K - Club Officer Workbook: President (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Circle K - Service Project Locator (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Circle K Misc. Papers (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - CSL Guidelines (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Council of Clubs By-laws (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Habitat for Humanity Presentation (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Marist Singers By-laws Revision (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - SGA Guidelines (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - SIFE Bylaws (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - SPC By-laws (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 32.3: Events
    - Miles for Medals Walk (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller Center Tour (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - RSC/Gaelic Society Trip Allocations (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 32.4: Reports
    - Student Guidelines for an Appeal (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Student Traffic Court Interim Report (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 32.5: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Student Academic Committee Student Correspondence Forms (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 32.6: Misc.
    - Application for Appointment in the SGA - Beth Mathewson (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - DUCSA Files (Floppy disk) (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Applications for Student Gov. (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Club Faculty Advisor of the Year Application Form (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Meeting Follow-up Sheets (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Notes (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Power Joint Meeting Procedure Outline (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Schedule of Events (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Senate Applications (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - SGA Structure (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - SGA Survey (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Student Union Flyer (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - "Top 10 Things" Papers (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Undated Meetings Notes (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Valentine's Packages (Box 28, Folder 41)